American Federation of Labor Records, Part 2 on Microfilm 5760 mf
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Convention File, 1935-1952 (Reel 5)
  - 0892. Box 7/Folder 1. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention - Labor's League for Political Education. 170 pages., 1947-1948; 30 (Reel 5)
- Convention File, 1935-1952 (Reel 6)
  - 0001. Box 7/Folder 2. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention - Labor Paper (Daily). 32 pages., 1947-1948; 1 (Reel 6)
  - 0033. Box 7/Folder 3. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention - International Labor Relations - Latin America. 264 pages., 1947-1948; 2 (Reel 6)
  - 0297. Box 7/Folder 4. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention. 63 pages., 1947-1948; 3 (Reel 6)
  - 0298. Box 7/Folder 4. Legislative Facilities. 2 pages., 1947; 4 (Reel 6)
  - 0300. Box 7/Folder 4. Longshoremen - Puerto Rico. 60 pages., 1947-1948; 5 (Reel 6)
  - 0360. Box 7/Folder 5. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention - Machinists' Union - Dissolution. 45 pages., 1947-1948; 6 (Reel 6)
  - 0405. Box 7/Folder 6. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention - Machinists' Union - Panama Canal Zone. 71 pages., 1947-1948; 7 (Reel 6)
  - 0474. Box 7/Folder 7. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention - Marshall Plan for European Recovery. 97 pages., 1947-1948; 8 (Reel 6)
  - 0571. Box 7/Folder 8. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention., 1947-1948; 9 (Reel 6)
  - 0572. Box 7/Folder 8. Military Governments, United States Representatives in. 2 pages., 1947; 10 (Reel 6)
  - 0574. Box 7/Folder 8. Miners - Court Case (U.S. versus John L. Lewis and United Mine Workers of America). 7 pages., 1947-1948; 11 (Reel 6)
  - 0581. Box 7/Folder 8. Minority Discrimination. 16 pages., 1947-1948; 12 (Reel 6)
  - 0597. Box 7/Folder 8. Miscellaneous - International Labor Relations. 82 pages., 1947-1948; 13 (Reel 6)
  - 0679. Box 7/Folder 8. Missouri Valley Development Plan. 20 pages., 1947-1948; 14 (Reel 6)
  - 0699. Box 7/Folder 8. National Labor Relations Board (NLRB), Biased Administration of. 6 pages., 1947-1948; 15 (Reel 6)
  - 0705. Box 7/Folder 8. New International Unions - Chartered. 2 pages., 1947; 16 (Reel 6)
  - 0707. Box 8/Folder 1. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention., 1947-1948; 17 (Reel 6)
  - 0708. Box 8/Folder 1. Newsprint - Supply for Labor Press. 10 pages., 1947-1948; 18 (Reel 6)
  - 0718. Box 8/Folder 1. Non-Communist Affidavits - Taft Hartley Act. 18 pages., 1947-1948; 19 (Reel 6)
  - 0736. Box 8/Folder 1. Organizing Activities and Official Changes. 54 pages., 1947-1948; 20 (Reel 6)
  - 0790. Box 8/Folder 1. Palestine - Trade Union Committee for Labor. 7 pages., 1947; 21 (Reel 6)
  - 0797. Box 8/Folder 1. Palm Springs - Anti-Labor Campaign. 2 pages., 1947-1948; 22 (Reel 6)
  - 0799. Box 8/Folder 1. Payroll Savings Plan, United States. 4 pages., 1947-1948; 23 (Reel 6)
  - 0803. Box 8/Folder 2. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention., 1947-1948; 24 (Reel 6)
  - 0804. Box 8/Folder 2. Postal Service. 5 pages., 1947; 25 (Reel 6)
  - 0809. Box 8/Folder 2. Prices and Price Control. 35 pages., 1947-1948; 26 (Reel 6)
  - 0834. Box 8/Folder 2. Public Relations - Program (Contract, etcetera). 68 pages., 1947-1948; 27 (Reel 6)
  - 0902. Box 8/Folder 3. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention - Public Relations - Committee on Publicity. 183 pages., 1947-1948; 28 (Reel 6)
- Convention File, 1935-1952 (Reel 7)
  - 0001. Box 8/Folder 4. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention., 1947; 1 (Reel 7)
  - 0002. Box 8/Folder 4. Puerto Rico - Free Federation of Workingmen. 10 pages., 1947; 2 (Reel 7)
  - 0012. Box 8/Folder 4. Puerto Rico - Committee to Study Conditions. 20 pages., 1947-1948; 3 (Reel 7)
  - 0032. Box 8/Folder 4. Railroad Signalmen - Reafilliation. 2 pages., 1947; 4 (Reel 7)
  - 0034. Box 8/Folder 4. Reports - Departments, Funds, Legal Activities. 54 pages., 1947; 5 (Reel 7)
  - 0088. Box 8/Folder 4. Retirement Plan - American Federation of Labor Employees. 13 pages., 1947; 6 (Reel 7)
  - 0101. Box 8/Folder 4. Social Security Service (American Federation of Labor), Expansion of. 2 pages., 1947; 7 (Reel 7)
  - 0103. Box 8/Folder 4. Sugar Workers - Suggested Conference. 5 pages., 1947; 8 (Reel 7)
  - 0108. Box 8/Folder 5. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention - Taft-Hartley Act. 167 pages., 1947-1948; 9 (Reel 7)
  - 0275. Box 8/Folder 6. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention - Taft-Hartley Act. 152 pages., 1948; 10 (Reel 7)
  - 0427. Box 9/Folder 1. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention., 1946-1948; 11 (Reel 7)
  - 0427. Box 9/Folder 1. Taft-Hartley Act. 58 pages., 1947-1948; 12 (Reel 7)
  - 0485. Box 9/Folder 1. Machinists - Continued Disassociation. 26 pages., 1946-1948; 13 (Reel 7)
  - 0511. Box 9/Folder 2. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention., 1947; 14 (Reel 7)
  - 0512. Box 9/Folder 2. Teacher Representation - United Nations Educational, Social, Cultural Organization (UNESCO). 17 pages., 1947; 15 (Reel 7)
  - 0529. Box 9/Folder 2. Territories, Organization Department for. 2 pages., 1947; 16 (Reel 7)
  - 0531. Box 9/Folder 2. Union Label Week. 2 pages., 1947; 17 (Reel 7)
  - 0533. Box 9/Folder 3. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention - United Nations - International Labor Organization (ILO). 160 pages., 1947- 1948; 18 (Reel 7)
  - 0693. Box 9/Folder 4. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention - United Nations - International Labor Organization. 202 pages., 1947- 1948; 19 (Reel 7)
  - 0895. Box 9/Folder 5. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention - United Nations - Economic and Social Council Reports. 168 pages., 1947- 1948; 20 (Reel 7)
- Convention File, 1935-1952 (Reel 8)
  - 0001. Box 9/Folder 6. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention - United Nations - Palestine. 165 pages., 1947-1948; 1 (Reel 8)
  - 0166. Box 9/Folder 7. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention., 1947-1948; 2 (Reel 8)
  - 0167. Box 9/Folder 7. United Nations - Slave Labor. 18 pages., 1947-1948; 3 (Reel 8)
  - 0185. Box 9/Folder 7. Vacations - 26 Days with Pay. 2 pages., 1947; 4 (Reel 8)
  - 0187. Box 9/Folder 7. "Westward Ho" Hotel - Strikebreakers. 5 pages., 1947; 5 (Reel 8)
  - 0192. Box 9/Folder 7. World Federation of Trade Unions. 17 pages., 1948; 6 (Reel 8)
  - 0209. Box 9/Folder 8. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention., 1947; 7 (Reel 8)
  - 0209. Box 9/Folder 8. Miscellaneous Resolutions of the Convention. 39 pages., 1947; 8 (Reel 8)
  - 0248. Box 9/Folder 8. Committee Appointments - No Action Necessary. 8 pages., 1947; 9 (Reel 8)
  - 0256. Box 10/Folder 1. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention., 1947-1948; 10 (Reel 8)
  - 0257. Box 10/Folder 1. American Book Company - Unfair to Labor. 3 pages., 1948; 11 (Reel 8)
  - 0260. Box 10/Folder 1. British Trades Union Congress - Fraternal Delegates. 83 pages., 1948; 12 (Reel 8)
  - 0343. Box 10/Folder 1. Bureau of Apprentice Training. 2 pages., 1948; 13 (Reel 8)
  - 0345. Box 10/Folder 1. Bureau of Labor Statistics - Industrial safety. 2 pages., 1948; 14 (Reel 8)
  - 0347. Box 10/Folder 1. Bureau of Labor Statistics, Approval for. 2 pages., 1948; 15 (Reel 8)
  - 0349. Box 10/Folder 1. Auditing and Credentials Committee. 14 pages., 1948; 16 (Reel 8)
  - 0363. Box 10/Folder 1. Campaign - 1948 Miscellaneous. 93 pages., 1947-1948; 17 (Reel 8)
  - 0456. Box 10/Folder 2. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention., 1948-1949; 18 (Reel 8)
  - 0457. Box 10/Folder 2. Chicago Transit Company. 2 pages., 1948; 19 (Reel 8)
  - 0459. Box 10/Folder 2. Civil Rights. 4 pages., 1948; 20 (Reel 8)
  - 0463. Box 10/Folder 2. Convention Material - Cincinnati. 52 pages., 1948; 21 (Reel 8)
  - 0505. Box 10/Folder 2. Cooperative Buying to Combat High Prices. 2 pages., 1948; 22 (Reel 8)
  - 0507. Box 10/Folder 2. Council for Cooperative Development. 16 pages., 1948; 23 (Reel 8)
  - 0523. Box 10/Folder 2. Crusade for Children - Support. 2 pages., 1948; 24 (Reel 8)
  - 0525. Box 10/Folder 2. Daily Labor Press. 17 pages., 1948; 25 (Reel 8)
  - 0542. Box 10/Folder 2. Discrimination against Youth of Draft Age by Industry. 4 pages., 1948-1949; 26 (Reel 8)
  - 0546. Box 10/Folder 3. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention - Economic Cooperation Administration (ECA). 238 pages., 1948-1949; 27 (Reel 8)
  - 0784. Box 10/Folder 4. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention., 1948-1949; 28 (Reel 8)
  - 0785. Box 10/Folder 4. Education Program (American Federation of Labor). 2 pages., 1948; 29 (Reel 8)
  - 0787. Box 10/Folder 4. Electoral College. 3 pages., 1948-1949; 30 (Reel 8)
  - 0790. Box 10/Folder 4. Engineers - Firemen and Oilers. 4 pages., 1948-1949; 31 (Reel 8)
  - 0794. Box 10/Folder 4. European Recovery Program - Trade Union Advisory Committee. 29 pages., 1948-1949; 32 (Reel 8)
  - 0823. Box 10/Folder 4. Executive Officers, Constitutional Amendments regarding. 4 pages., 1948; 33 (Reel 8)
  - 0827. Box 10/Folder 4. Federal Labor Union Council. 6 pages., 1948-1949; 34 (Reel 8)
  - 0833. Box 10/Folder 4. Free Trade Union Committee - Labor's League for Human Rights. 59 pages., 1949; 35 (Reel 8)
  - 0892. Box 10/Folder 4. Government Contracts, Recognition of Western Industries in. 2 pages., 1948-1949; 36 (Reel 8)
  - 0895. Box 10/Folder 4. Health and Safety Department - American Federation of Labor. 4 pages., 1948-1949; 37 (Reel 8)
  - 0899. Box 10/Folder 4. Infringement of Professional Societies upon International Federation of Technical Engineers, Architects, and Draftsmen's Union ( IFTEA and DU) Jurisdiction. 4 pages., 1948-1949; 38 (Reel 8)
  - 0903. Box 10/Folder 5. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention - International Labor Organization. 184 pages., 1948-1949; 39 (Reel 8)
- Convention File, 1935-1952 (Reel 9)
  - 0001. Box 11/Folder 1. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention - International Labor Relations - General File. 70 pages., 1948-1949; 1 (Reel 9)
  - 0071. Box 11/Folder 2. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention., 1948-1949; 2 (Reel 9)
  - 0072. Box 11/Folder 2. International Labor Relations - Austria. 7 pages., 1948-1949; 3 (Reel 9)
  - 0079. Box 11/Folder 2. International Labor Relations - China (Republic of China). 20 pages., 1948-1949; 4 (Reel 9)
  - 0099. Box 11/Folder 2. International Labor Relations - Czechoslovakia. 1 page., 1949; 5 (Reel 9)
  - 0100. Box 11/Folder 2. International Labor Relations - France. 11 pages., 1948-1949; 6 (Reel 9)
  - 0111. Box 11/Folder 2. International Labor Relations - Great Britain. 2 pages., 1949; 7 (Reel 9)
  - 0113. Box 11/Folder 2. International Labor Relations - Latin America. 1 page., 1949; 8 (Reel 9)
  - 0114. Box 11/Folder 2. International Labor Relations - Guam. 4 pages., 1949; 9 (Reel 9)
  - 0118. Box 11/Folder 2. International Labor Relations - Hungary. 2 pages., 1948; 10 (Reel 9)
  - 0120. Box 11/Folder 2. International Labor Relations - India. 63 pages., 1948-1949; 11 (Reel 9)
  - 0183. Box 11/Folder 2. International Labor Relations - Indonesia. 2 pages., 1948; 12 (Reel 9)
  - 0185. Box 11/Folder 2. International Labor Relations - Israel. 3 pages., 1949; 13 (Reel 9)
  - 0188. Box 11/Folder 2. International Labor Relations - China (Russian Refugees). 8 pages., 1949; 14 (Reel 9)
  - 0196. Box 11/Folder 2. International Labor Relations - Transport Workers' Federation. 2 pages., 1949; 15 (Reel 9)
  - 0198. Box 11/Folder 2. International Labor Relations - Italy. 9 pages., 1948-1949; 16 (Reel 9)
  - 0207. Box 11/Folder 2. International Labor Relations - Japan. 10 pages., 1948-1949; 17 (Reel 9)
  - 0217. Box 11/Folder 2. International Labor Relations - Korea (Republic of Korea). 4 pages., 1949; 18 (Reel 9)
  - 0221. Box 11/Folder 2. International Labor Relations - Netherlands. 1 page., 1949; 19 (Reel 9)
  - 0222. Box 11/Folder 2. International Labor Relations Poland. 28 pages., 1948-1949; 20 (Reel 9)
  - 0250. Box 11/Folder 2. International Labor Relations - Spain. 53 pages., 1948-1949; 21 (Reel 9)
  - 0303. Box 11/Folder 2. International Labor Relations - Latin America. 1 page., 1949; 22 (Reel 9)
  - 0304. Box 11/Folder 3. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention., 1948-1949; 23 (Reel 9)
  - 0305. Box 11/Folder 3. International Labor Relations - Germany. 113 pages., 1948-1949; 24 (Reel 9)
  - 0418. Box 11/Folder 3. International Labor Relations - Greece. 43 pages., 1948-1949; 25 (Reel 9)
  - 0461. Box 11/Folder 4. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention, 1948-1949; 26 (Reel 9)
  - 0462. Box 11/Folder 4. International Trade Union Secretariats. 5 pages., 1948; 27 (Reel 9)
  - 0467. Box 11/Folder 4. Italian-American Labor Council. 2 pages., 1948; 28 (Reel 9)
  - 0469. Box 11/Folder 4. Jewish Labor Council. 2 pages., 1948; 29 (Reel 9)
  - 0471. Box 11/Folder 4. Jurisdictional Disputes. 2 pages., 1948; 30 (Reel 9)
  - 0473. Box 11/Folder 4. Jurisdiction - Sailors Union. 3 pages., 1948; 31 (Reel 9)
  - 0476. Box 11/Folder 4. Labor's League for Political Education. 67 pages., 1948-1949; 32 (Reel 9)
  - 0543. Box 11/Folder 4. Labor Unity. 15 pages., 1948-1949; 33 (Reel 9)
  - 0558. Box 11/Folder 4. Latin American Confederation of Workers (C.I.T.). 67 pages., 1948-1949; 34 (Reel 9)
  - 0651. Box 11/Folder 5. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention., 1948-1950; 35 (Reel 9)
  - 0652. Box 11/Folder 5. Legislative Committee - Expansion. 2 pages., 1948; 36 (Reel 9)
  - 0654. Box 11/Folder 5. Local Union - Affiliation with State Federations and Central Labor Unions. 13 pages., 1948-1950; 37 (Reel 9)
  - 0667. Box 11/Folder 5. Miami Beach Union Organization - Hotel and Restaurant Employees. 11 pages., 1948-1949; 38 (Reel 9)
  - 0678. Box 11/Folder 5. National Legislative Council. 95 pages., 1948-1949; 39 (Reel 9)
  - 0773. Box 11/Folder 6. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention., 1946-1949; 40 (Reel 9)
  - 0774. Box 11/Folder 6. Peter J. McGuire Memorial. 19 pages., 1946-1949; 41 (Reel 9)
  - 0793. Box 11/Folder 6. Political Action - New Political Party. 4 pages., 1948; 42 (Reel 9)
  - 0797. Box 11/Folder 6. Organization - Forestry Workers. 3 pages., 1948-1949; 43 (Reel 9)
  - 0800. Box 11/Folder 6. Organizers (Additional) - Alaska. 20 pages., 1948-1949; 44 (Reel 9)
  - 0820. Box 11/Folder 6. Palestine. 8 pages., 1948-1949; 45 (Reel 9)
  - 0828. Box 11/Folder 6. Peter J. McGuire Memorial. 3 pages., 1948; 46 (Reel 9)
  - 0831. Box 11/Folder 6. Political Action - New Political Party. 3 pages., 1948; 47 (Reel 9)
  - 0834. Box 11/Folder 6. Publicity - Radio and Labor Press. 54 pages., 1947-1949; 48 (Reel 9)
  - 0889. Box 11/Folder 6. Public Relations Program. 2 pages., 1948; 49 (Reel 9)
  - 0891. Box 12/Folder 1. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention., 1948-1950; 50 (Reel 9)
  - 0892. Box 12/Folder 1. Reports - Departments, Organization, and Campaigns. 90 pages., 1948-1950; 51 (Reel 9)
  - 0981. Box 12/Folder 1. Resolutions - Reference and Subjects for Attention. 12 pages., 1948; 52 (Reel 9)
  - 0993. Box 12/Folder 1. Speakers Invited to Address Convention. 65 pages., 1948; 53 (Reel 9)
- Convention File, 1935-1952. (Reel 10)
  - 0001. Box 12/Folder 2. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention., 1948-1949; 1 (Reel 10)
  - 0002. Box 12/Folder 2. State Federations of Labor - Affiliations. 16 pages., 1948-1949; 2 (Reel 10)
  - 0018. Box 12/Folder 2. Strike Benefits. 5 pages., 1948-1949; 3 (Reel 10)
  - 0023. Box 12/Folder 4. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention - Taft-Harley Act (Labor Legislation). 128 pages., 1948-1949; 4 (Reel 10)
  - 0151. Box 12/Folder 4. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention - Taft-Hartley Act (Miscellaneous). 128 pages., 1947-1950; 5 (Reel 10)
  - 0279. Box 12/Folder 5. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention., 1947-1949; 6 (Reel 10)
  - 0280. Box 12/Folder 5. Commercial Telegraphers - Support. 13 pages., 1948-1949; 7 (Reel 10)
  - 0293. Box 12/Folder 5. United Nations - UNESCO and General. 127 pages., 1947-1949; 8 (Reel 10)
  - 0420. Box 12/Folder 5. Trade Union Fellowship Program. 3 pages., 1948-1949; 9 (Reel 10)
  - 0423. Box 12/Folder 5. War Department - Engraved Certificate. 2 pages., 1948; 10 (Reel 10)
  - 0425. Box 12/Folder 6. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention., 1948-1949; 11 (Reel 10)
  - 0426. Box 12/Folder 6. Proposed New World Federation of Labor. 142 pages., 1949; 12 (Reel 10)
  - 0468. Box 12/Folder 6. World Federation of Trade Unions. 32 pages., 1948-1949; 13 (Reel 10)
  - 0600. Box 12/Folder 7. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention - Resolutions - No Action Necessary and Non-Concurred. 20 pages., 1948; 14 (Reel 10)
  - 0620. Box 13/Folder 1. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention., 1949-1950; 15 (Reel 10)
  - 0621. Box 13/Folder 1. Aid to Typographical Union. 9 pages., 1949; 16 (Reel 10)
  - 0630. Box 13/Folder 1. apprenticeship Committee. 2 pages., 1949; 17 (Reel 10)
  - 0632. Box 13/Folder 1. Auditing and Credentials Committee. 12 pages., 1949; 18 (Reel 10)
  - 0644. Box 13/Folder 1. Building Trades - Union Button. 5 pages., 1949-1950; 19 (Reel 10)
  - 0649. Box 13/Folder 1. Bureau of apprenticeship. 2 pages., 1949; 20 (Reel 10)
  - 0651. Box 13/Folder 1. Bureau of Labor Standards. 2 pages., 1949; 21 (Reel 10)
  - 0653. Box 13/Folder 1. Bureau of Labor Statistics. 2 pages., 1949; 22 (Reel 10)
  - 0655. Box 13/Folder 1. Community Chests. 16 pages., 1949-1950; 23 (Reel 10)
  - 0671. Box 13/Folder 1. Conscientious Objectors. 17 pages., 1949-1950; 24 (Reel 10)
  - 0688. Box 13/Folder 1. Convention Date Change. 4 pages., 1949; 25 (Reel 10)
  - 0692. Box 13/Folder 1. Election Day Holiday. 2 pages., 1949; 26 (Reel 10)
  - 0694. Box 13/Folder 2. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention., 1949-1950; 27 (Reel 10)
  - 0695. Box 13/Folder 2. Federal Labor Union - Council. 5 pages., 1949; 28 (Reel 10)
  - 0700. Box 13/Folder 2. Federal Labor Union - Principle. 3 pages., 1949; 29 (Reel 10)
  - 0703. Box 13/Folder 2. Firefighters - Panama Canal Zone. 4 pages., 1949; 30 (Reel 10)
  - 0707. Box 13/Folder 2. Fishing Commission - International. 32 pages., 1949-1950; 31 (Reel 10)
  - 0739. Box 13/Folder 2. Flag Day - Observance. 9 pages., 1949; 32 (Reel 10)
  - 0748. Box 13/Folder 3. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention - Economic Cooperation Administration (ECA) - European Recovery Plan. 215 pages., 1949-1950; 33 (Reel 10)
- Convention File, 1935-1952 (Reel 11)
  - 0001. Box 13/Folder 4. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention., 1948-1950; 1 (Reel 11)
  - 0002. Box 13/Folder 4. Fraternal Delegates. 63 pages., 1948-1949; 2 (Reel 11)
  - 0065. Box 13/Folder 4. Gompers Centenary. 72 pages., 1949-1950; 3 (Reel 11)
  - 0137. Box 13/Folder 4. Hawaii - Aid to American Federation of Labor Unions. 9 pages., 1949-1950; 4 (Reel 11)
  - 0146. Box 13/Folder 4. History of American Federation of Labor - Proposed. 6 pages., 1949-1950; 5 (Reel 11)
  - 0152. Box 13/Folder 4. History of American Federation of Labor - Film. 18 pages., 1949-1950; 6 (Reel 11)
  - 0170. Box 13/Folder 4. Indiana - Organizing Staff. 2 pages., 1949; 7 (Reel 11)
  - 0172. Box 13/Folder 4. Ireland, Partition of. 12 pages., 1949-1950; 8 (Reel 11)
  - 0184. Box 13/Folder 4. Israel. 24 pages., 1949-1950; 9 (Reel 11)
  - 0208. Box 13/Folder 4. Italian-American Labor Council. 2 pages., 1949; 10 (Reel 11)
  - 0210. Box 13/Folder 4. Italy, free Trade Unionism in. 2 pages., 1949; 11 (Reel 11)
  - 0212. Box 14/Folder 1. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention., 1949-1951; 12 (Reel 11)
  - 0213. Box 14/Folder 1. International Confederation of Free Trade Unions (ICFTU) - General. 96 pages., 1950; 13 (Reel 11)
  - 0309. Box 14/Folder 1. ICFTU - London 1949 Meeting. 51 pages., 1949-1950; 14 (Reel 11)
  - 0358. Box 14/Folder 1. ICFTU - Africa. 35 pages., 1950-1951; 15 (Reel 11)
  - 0393. Box 14/Folder 2. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention - ICFTU - London 1949 Meeting (Special Material for President Green). 120 pages., 1944-1949; 16 (Reel 11)
  - 0514. Box 14/Folder 3. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention - ICFTU - Miscellaneous. 51 pages., 1949-1950; 17 (Reel 11)
  - 0565. Box 14/Folder 4. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention - ICFTU - Conferences. 133 pages., 1949-1950; 18 (Reel 11)
  - 0699. Box 14/Folder 5. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention - ICFTU - Executive Board. 139 pages., 1950; 19 (Reel 11)
  - 0837. Box 14/Folder 6. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention - International Labor Organization (ILO). 111 pages., 1949-1950; 20 (Reel 11)
- Convention File, 1935-1952 (Reel 12)
  - 0001. Box 15/Folder 1. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention - International Labor Relations - General. 71 pages., 1949-1950; 1 (Reel 12)
  - 0072. Box 15/Folder 2. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention., 1949-1950; 2 (Reel 12)
  - 0073. Box 15/Folder 2.. International Labor Relations - China. 41 pages., 1949-1950; 3 (Reel 12)
  - 0114. Box 15/Folder 2. International Labor Relations - Finland. 9 pages., 1949; 4 (Reel 12)
  - 0123. Box 15/Folder 2. International Labor Relations - France. 31 pages., 1949-1950; 5 (Reel 12)
  - 0154. Box 15/Folder 2. International Labor Relations - Germany. 123 pages., 1949-1950; 6 (Reel 12)
  - 0277. Box 15/Folder 2. International Labor Relations - Greece. 61 pages., 1949-1950; 7 (Reel 12)
  - 0338. Box 15/Folder 3. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention., 1948-1950; 8 (Reel 12)
  - 0339. Box 15/Folder 3. International Labor Relations - Hungary. 2 pages., 1950; 9 (Reel 12)
  - 0341. Box 15/Folder 3. International Labor Relations - India. 78 pages., 1949; 10 (Reel 12)
  - 0419. Box 15/Folder 3. International Labor Relations - Indonesia. 23 pages., 1948-1949; 11 (Reel 12)
  - 0442. Box 15/Folder 3. International Labor Relations - Israel. 6 pages., 1949; 12 (Reel 12)
  - 0448. Box 15/Folder 3. International Labor Relations - Italy. 22 pages., 1949-1950; 13 (Reel 12)
  - 0470. Box 15/Folder 3. International Labor Relations - Japan. 38 pages., 1949-1950; 14 (Reel 12)
  - 0508. Box 15/Folder 3. International Labor Relations - Korea (ROK). 18 pages., 1949-1950; 15 (Reel 12)
  - 0526. Box 15/Folder 3. International Labor Relations - Norway. 2 pages., 1949; 16 (Reel 12)
  - 0528. Box 15/Folder 3. International Labor Relations - Pakistan. 4 pages., 1950; 17 (Reel 12)
  - 0532. Box 15/Folder 3. International Labor Relations - Poland. 6 pages., 1950; 18 (Reel 12)
  - 0538. Box 15/Folder 3. International Labor Relations - Serbia. 7 pages., 1950; 19 (Reel 12)
  - 0545. Box 15/Folder 3. International Labor Relations - Spain. 56 pages., 1949-1950; 20 (Reel 12)
  - 0601. Box 15/Folder 4. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention. 188 pages., 1948-1950; 21 (Reel 12)
  - 0602. Box 15/Folder 4. New International Unions Chartered. 2 pages., 1948-1949; 22 (Reel 12)
  - 0604. Box 15/Folder 4. Jewish Labor Committee. 2 pages., 1949; 23 (Reel 12)
  - 0606. Box 15/Folder 4. Labor Films, Proposed. 3 pages., 1949-1950; 24 (Reel 12)
  - 0609. Labor's League for Political Education. 115 pages., 1949-1950; 25 (Reel 12)
  - 0714. Box 15/Folder 4. Labor Paper - National. 3 pages., 1949-1950; 26 (Reel 12)
  - 0717. Box 15/Folder 4. Latin American Activities. 72 pages., 1949-1950; 27 (Reel 12)
  - 0789. Box 16/Folder 1. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention., 1949-1950; 28 (Reel 12)
  - 0790. Box 16/Folder 1. Legal Activities. 61 pages., 1949-1950; 29 (Reel 12)
  - 0851. Box 16/Folder 1. Literature - Distribution. 2 pages., 1949; 30 (Reel 12)
  - 0853. Box 16/Folder 1. Machinists - Proposed Reafilliation. 69 pages., 1949-1950; 31 (Reel 12)
  - 0922. Box 16/Folder 1. Minneapolis - Wage and Hour Regional Office. 18 pages., 1949; 32 (Reel 12)
- Convention File, 1935-1952 (Reel 13)
  - 0001. Box 16/Folder 2. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention., 1949-1950; 1 (Reel 13)